Spiders make their presence felt in late August and through early autumn.
在8月下旬以及整个初秋，蜘蛛都会让人感觉到它们的存在。
This is the mating season of some of the most common varieties, when male house spiders come out of hidden corners to look for females, and garden spiders reach adult size and spin their most dazzling webs.
此时正值几种最常见蜘蛛的交配季节：雄性家隅蛛会从隐蔽的角落里钻出来寻找雌蛛，园蛛则长到成年大小，织出最炫目的网。
Yet while the spider is a familiar fixture of nursery poems or songs and Halloween decorations, its relationship with humans is complicated.
然而，尽管蜘蛛是童诗、儿歌和万圣节装饰中的常客，它与人类的关系却很复杂。
Fear of spiders is common and has serious impacts on the lives of sufferers.
对蜘蛛的恐惧很普遍，严重影响着患者的生活。
Its prevalence appears unrelated to any rational assessment of risk.
这种恐惧的普遍程度，似乎与对风险的任何理性评估都毫无关联。
Spiders in the UK are almost all harmless.
英国的蜘蛛几乎全都无害。
Farmland species perform valuable ecosystem services, by preying on insects that are our competitors for crops.
农田里的蜘蛛物种通过捕食与我们争夺庄稼的昆虫，提供宝贵的生态系统服务。
But they are a constant source of human anxieties—with a cultural association with witches and wickedness dating back to the Middle Ages.
但蜘蛛始终是人类焦虑的一个来源——它们在文化上与女巫和邪恶联系在一起，这种关联可以追溯到中世纪。
Does this perhaps explain, in part, the lack of data about how spiders are faring in our age of ecological crisis?
这会不会在一定程度上解释了，为什么蜘蛛在我们这个生态危机时代的生存状况缺乏数据？
British butterflies are the most studied group of insects in the world, due to the long tradition of collecting and observing them.
英国蝴蝶是世界上研究得最多的昆虫类群，因为收集和观察蝴蝶在英国有着悠久的传统。
But spider conservationists point out that it was only in the 1980s that the classification of house spiders was properly sorted out.
但蜘蛛保护人士指出，直到20世纪80年代，家隅蛛的分类才真正理清。
And while information about insect populations is gathered by experiments that measure the numbers hitting windscreens or traps, there have been few attempts to count spiders.
而且，虽然人们通过实验来收集有关昆虫种群的信息，测算撞上挡风玻璃或落入诱捕器的昆虫数量，但迄今很少有人尝试统计蜘蛛的数量。
The huge reductions in the numbers of flying insects can only mean a reduction in spiders’ food supply.
飞虫数量大幅减少，只能意味着蜘蛛的食物供应减少。
A recent landmark study identified a 75% fall in insect populations between 1989 and 2016, with pesticide use thought to be to blame along with the destruction of wild areas for development.
最近一项具有里程碑意义的研究发现，1989年至2016年间，昆虫种群数量下降了75%，人们认为，这要归咎于使用农药以及为开发而破坏荒野地区。
This means the overall picture for spiders is worrying, as it is for most creatures.
这意味着，蜘蛛的总体状况令人担忧，大多数生物的情况也是如此。
But conservationists are most concerned about those varieties that are threatened due to habitat loss and fragmentation, which makes it impossible for them to migrate.
但保护人士最担心的，是那些因栖息地丧失和碎片化而受到威胁的种类，这种状况使它们无法迁移。
Of around 650 spider species regularly recorded in the UK, the majority thrive in marshes and wasteland.
在英国经常有记录的约650种蜘蛛中，大多数都在沼泽和荒地里繁衍兴旺。
Conservation efforts, often led by determined individuals, have helped some species to recover by reintroducing them to new areas.
保护工作往往由意志坚定的个人牵头，通过把一些物种重新引入新的地区，已经帮助它们恢复过来。
With rewilding now firmly on the environmental policy agenda, the hope is that in future, spiders will be enabled to migrate by themselves, adapting to climate change by moving along wildlife corridors.
如今，再野化已牢牢列入环境政策议程，人们希望将来蜘蛛能够自行迁移，沿着野生动物走廊移动，从而适应气候变化。
It seems unlikely that spiders will ever attract the same level of human enthusiasm as bees, birds or butterflies, in spite of their unique status as nature’s spinners.
尽管蜘蛛作为大自然的吐丝者地位独特，但它们似乎不太可能有朝一日像蜜蜂、鸟类或蝴蝶那样，激起人类同等程度的热情。
But as they reveal themselves in all their splendour this autumn, it would be a good thing if more animal lovers recognised the ways in which spiders are simply terrific.
但今年秋天，在蜘蛛尽显风采之际，如果有更多动物爱好者认识到蜘蛛在种种方面实在了不起，那将是一件好事。